<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<add>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">A Saudi princess jailed without charges since March 2019 has made a rare public appeal to the king and crown prince for her release out of fear of coronavirus infection, exposing long-simmering tensions in the Saudi royal family https://t.co/vjbm5hJl9E</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-17 07:45:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">President Trump outlined new federal guidelines for opening up the country in three phases that will put the onus on governors to decide how to restart the economies in their states https://t.co/MGAqkTkK3J</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-17 07:30:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">From @WSJopinion: From the start of the crisis, WHO leadership let political considerations color what should have been unbiased public-health advice https://t.co/ehgFJSuag6</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-17 07:15:08</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Emmy award-winning journalist Meredith Vieira shares advice with women on how to ask for what they want in the workplace. #WSJWhatsNow https://t.co/N7sJ52ziXh</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-17 07:00:01</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The coronavirus pandemic is cutting into supermarket meat supplies and affecting choices available in meat cases as plant workers get sick, making it tougher for meat packers to meet surging demand https://t.co/uz80mrZV1E</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-17 06:45:03</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Brian Dennehy, the burly actor who started in films such as "First Blood" and later in his career won plaudits for his stage work, has died. He was 81. https://t.co/oX1vko5em8</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-17 06:15:08</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Watch live: President Trump is expected to outline at today's White House briefing new federal guidelines for opening up the country https://t.co/0EEHzrdZjJ</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-17 06:08:30</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Wuhan has started testing for antibodies among thousands of people returning to work, and others without symptoms, to gain a clearer picture of immunity levels in the city and try to prevent a second wave of disease https://t.co/Z7GAfquzgp</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-17 06:00:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">President Jair Bolsonaro, who has insisted the risk from the coronavirus is low and called for Brazil to stay open for business, fired his health minister Thursday after the two clashed repeatedly over how to handle the pandemic https://t.co/SAgngSd13O</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-17 05:45:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Amazon, struggling to meet an immense surge in order volumes and contending with worker absences during the coronavirus pandemic, is taking steps to persuade shoppers to put fewer items in their carts https://t.co/uenNNE7DRF</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-17 05:30:09</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">??? Hear how the sounds have changed in other cities as day-to-day living has been upended https://t.co/6kppAK9f5U</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-17 05:04:51</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">? After: Near the shores of Venice Beach in early April, the area was deserted https://t.co/6kppAK9f5U https://t.co/xY4OsGRRyl</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-17 05:00:57</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">? Before: Venice Beach in Los Angeles usually sees heavy traffic from beachgoers and passersby, heard in audio from last summer https://t.co/6kppAK9f5U https://t.co/dNfXKComCZ</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-17 04:58:30</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">? After: One of the French Quarter's most active strips, Bourbon Street, was largely empty in late March. The music of a distant street performer was the only sound heard. https://t.co/6kppAK9f5U https://t.co/m14jzTXCxZ</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-17 04:55:37</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">? Before: Cheers from Mardi Gras celebrations and crowds of tourists filled the streets in New Orleans' French Quarter last year https://t.co/6kppAK9f5U https://t.co/JEeDkG07ga</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-17 04:52:36</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">? After: Now it's hard to even distinguish footsteps over the jazz playing from Penn Station's public-address system https://t.co/C5zFBmaeH3</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-17 04:50:41</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">? Before: New York City's Penn Station typically bustled with passengers packed inside the transportation hub https://t.co/6kppAK9f5U https://t.co/ancyjxHe9G</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-17 04:48:01</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">??? With stay-at-home orders in place across the country and many businesses closed, once-lively locations have quieted. Listen to how the coronavirus pandemic has changed the sounds of our cities. https://t.co/4XX8FTXP39</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-17 04:44:31</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Zoom Video Communications is calling in the equivalent of the cybersecurity cavalry after security lapses that have drawn attention from authorities https://t.co/IcNRQv4r0F</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-17 04:29:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">From @WSJopinion: By clearing the regulatory path for academic research labs, we can help citizens have a better chance in the fight against Covid-19, write Jack W. Lipton and Caryl E. Sortwell of @MSUMD. https://t.co/g5Ytn1MIFc</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-17 04:15:06</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Trump's new guidelines to reopen the economy will put the onus on governors and won't suggest dates, a White House official says https://t.co/hxdGiG2e4N</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-17 03:41:55</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Shoppers used to getting packages in a matter of days on Amazon are now waiting for up to a month. @nicnguyen reports shopping small might be the solution. #WSJWhatsNow https://t.co/Wy2nlZVdW1 https://t.co/LZIq92zq3V</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-17 03:30:00</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Democrats view their strong first-quarter fundraising for key races as a sign they could flip the Senate, where Republicans hold a 53-47 majority https://t.co/7Ft5kJXDZr</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-17 03:15:09</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The Pentagon is getting a push to shift resources to Asia via a bill that would require the military to dedicate $6 billion a year to counter China and work with U.S. allies https://t.co/DimKREdUAM</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-17 02:30:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">More than 60 people have died at a New Jersey nursing home in one of the deadliest outbreaks involving long-term care facilities in the U.S. since the coronavirus pandemic first hit the country https://t.co/e3VgpuSOV0</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-17 02:15:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">#WSJWhatsNow: U.S. stocks are swinging between gains and losses after data showed another spike in the number of Americans seeking jobless benefits https://t.co/A2CKNjk5ks</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-17 01:45:00</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Americans are checking their bank accounts for the stimulus payments and some are surprised at how much or how little they got  https://t.co/lGNaJVNSgW</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-17 01:29:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Another 5.2 million Americans filed for unemployment benefits last week, bringing the total seeking aid in a month of coronavirus-related shutdowns to 22 million workers and showing a broad shock for the U.S. labor market https://t.co/v7Obi9FRtJ</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-17 12:45:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Should the U.S. build self-quarantine facilities for coronavirus patients with mild symptoms? @GeraldFSeib explains what it means to self-quarantine at home. #WSJWhatsNow https://t.co/eVCLQimLpa</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-17 12:00:01</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Amazon has started building a testing capacity to diagnose all employees for Covid-19, including those who display no symptoms, Chief Executive Jeffrey Bezos said in a shareholder letter https://t.co/ycuw7PcbNY</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 11:45:04</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Significant restrictions to cross-border traffic between the U.S. and Mexico, plus the social-distancing mandates around the U.S., appear to be making it harder to transport and deal illegal drugs inconspicuously, the acting DEA administrator said https://t.co/NPUuCnPd4b</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 11:30:16</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The Texas showdown over voting by mail amid coronavirus comes as Republicans and Democrats in other states have moved to extend absentee voting https://t.co/XsApTfkF3V</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 11:00:18</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Funding has been exhausted for the $350 billion Paycheck Protection Program as talks continue on adding funds to the small-business relief plan https://t.co/UAgRG909Cm</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 10:52:28</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Shoemakers churning out masks. Auto giants manufacturing ventilators. This is how the private sector goes to battle against a pandemic. https://t.co/yO4myAyiHX</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 10:30:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">From @WSJopinion: Americans relying on the Paycheck Protection Program need more funding, not more bureaucratic hurdles, write @GOPLeader and @SenatorTimScott https://t.co/osRsUwf5Bw</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 10:15:06</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">With stay-at-home orders in place across the country and many businesses closed, once-lively locations have quieted and sounds surrounding us have changed. https://t.co/0btaiCLCtf https://t.co/kRaenKC0Yi</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 10:00:14</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Verizon has agreed to buy videoconferencing company Blue Jeans Network as an unprecedented number of people work remotely because of the coronavirus pandemic https://t.co/byDR2jDsrK</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 09:38:02</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Breaking: Another 5.2 million workers filed for unemployment benefits last week, raising the total in a month of coronavirus shutdowns to more than 20 million https://t.co/6thSZAtg70</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 08:32:58</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">New data show how chunks of the U.S. economy froze in March, business executives tell President Trump that a lot more coronavirus testing is needed to get Americans back to work, and New York is set to require people to wear face coverings in public #WSJWhatsNow https://t.co/7QdutxnL5u</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 08:00:00</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Stock prices suggest a short recession with a swift rebound in corporate profits, while gains in havens signal worries about a longer downturn https://t.co/12HRpkYw1B</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 07:50:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">President Jair Bolsonaro wants to open Brazil's economy while his health minister urges no letup on social distancing as the virus spreads https://t.co/3qtYfs5KJO</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 06:45:04</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Confirmed cases globally have passed 2.06 million, about a third of them in the U.S., which has logged over 30,000 of the more than 137,000 deaths world-wide https://t.co/E2QFKJkIdf</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 06:30:06</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Face masks and coronavirus test kits bound for the U.S. are stuck in China because of new export restrictions, State Department memos say https://t.co/Ino7CEjplS</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 06:15:06</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The retailer Gap, which recently furloughed 80,000 workers, is encouraging those employees to take temporary part-time jobs, including at CVS https://t.co/m2d7vecwvV</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 05:45:03</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The Chinese-Japanese rivalry over favipiravir is an example of how coronavirus treatments have become a political as well as a medical issue https://t.co/lhxZ3uUj1g</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 05:37:25</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Take an early look at the front page of The Wall Street Journal https://t.co/5xQPDPcm8q https://t.co/ZFJU8mtJhh</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 05:15:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Federal aid will only buy airlines a few months. Their survival depends on how quickly passengers return when coronavirus-driven restrictions ease. https://t.co/qvBPsUp2Fr</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 04:30:08</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Indian startup Oyo Hotels &amp; Homes is planning to move some employees off its payroll and onto the rolls of its biggest investor, SoftBank, to cut costs https://t.co/wEUDfz92fL</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 04:15:03</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Food waste and empty shelves during coronavirus lockdowns show the challenge of switching goods between supply chains https://t.co/5rPKzjA1Cj</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 03:30:08</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Tracking coronavirus patients and their contacts using cellphone data. Drones monitoring public spaces for quarantine scofflaws. Virtual fences around isolation zones. How much public-health surveillance is too much? https://t.co/NeWsozIVYY</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 02:30:09</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The top 10 Midwestern colleges for student outcomes are evenly split between private and public schools https://t.co/4nh3hc7sec</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 02:00:10</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Pilates on Zoom, dances on TikTok...whatever home exercise you choose, the experts say good form is a must for avoiding aches and pains https://t.co/w2reX5cdAI</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 01:30:08</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Evidence of the economic damage caused by the coronavirus pandemic is building, putting pressure on markets https://t.co/Gtb1ioNkW3</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 01:00:09</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Take an early look at the front page of The Wall Street Journal https://t.co/5xQPDPcm8q https://t.co/7tz0YyJA7w</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 12:45:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Best-selling crime novelist Don Winslow on why it's not a bad idea to keep a punching bag in your office https://t.co/04y8O3bmUE</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 12:30:09</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Some crematory operators are handling triple the number of bodies they would on a typical day https://t.co/E6cL8hjjar</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 12:00:03</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">No bar tools, no worries: These hacks produce quality cocktails at home. https://t.co/pFbtLkL04C</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 11:45:04</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Officials are increasingly certain the coronavirus outbreak aboard aircraft carrier Theodore Roosevelt was sparked by flight crews, not a port visit https://t.co/16BxIp9c5S</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 11:00:16</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Superstar music producers Timbaland and Swizz Beatz are drawing hundreds of thousands of people on Instagram Live to watch them "battle" song for song https://t.co/Wa2r6Bs7UT</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 10:15:03</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The WHO called for nations to work together to defeat the coronavirus after Trump's funding threat and said it would seek to fill financing gaps from other donors https://t.co/HYvR5S4ErP</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 09:30:12</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Smithfield said it would close two more pork-processing plants because of the coronavirus pandemic, reducing meat supplies for grocery stores https://t.co/yvIR0nbn1V</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 09:15:06</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The coronavirus pandemic has resurrected national boundaries that had all but faded away, upending businesses and lives. Perhaps nowhere is the change more dramatic than in Europe. https://t.co/9VHSBECuxB</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 09:00:10</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">From @WSJopinion: Federal borrowing this year is set to pass 20% of U.S. GDP. Government risks consuming the oxygen that a powerful recovery will need, write Phil Gramm and Michael Solon. https://t.co/a2eVAXJfAI</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 08:45:06</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">New York City faces its worst fiscal crisis since the 1970s because of the coronavirus pandemic, according to a new report https://t.co/o62Si60Vkx</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 08:15:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Security professionals say the coronavirus crisis could become a watershed moment in the history of government surveillance  https://t.co/gHFlBHz7u5</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 08:00:20</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Can anyone who wants a coronavirus test get one? WSJ is updating this guide regularly with what we learn about the state of testing and treatment https://t.co/KYW0VeBuWW</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 07:45:02</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Here are some of the best ways to help those who are caring for someone with coronavirus, according to a woman whose husband was infected and hospitalized https://t.co/rH540nhXai</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 07:30:08</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">When stock-market circuit breakers are triggered, all trading is halted. Circuit breaking was created as guardrails for wild market moves. But today, some question how well they work. #WSJWhatsNow https://t.co/onJEwpT2MO</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 07:00:00</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">? Listen: In today's episode of The Journal podcast, @_melaevans explains why hospitals across the country are facing financial pain as the coronavirus floods them with patients https://t.co/nspH9ywcxA</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 06:45:08</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Deliveries are safer during the coronavirus pandemic, but a store run may be unavoidable. Here are the precautions to take. https://t.co/9hfLilD98V</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 06:31:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">After spring disruptions due to coronavirus social limits, the College Board and ACT are making plans so high-school students can take college-admission exams come fall https://t.co/Rk6Yz8HvoJ</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 06:16:06</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Turning the heat up. Using the noisy ice dispenser. People used to working at home are losing patience with the coronavirus newcomers.
https://t.co/Tn1HSxwmlQ</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 06:00:23</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">A growing number of Americans are paying rent by credit card during the coronavirus pandemic, a move that is enabling more tenants to make timely payments but potentially pushing some deeper into debt https://t.co/i5gGBWLD6b</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 05:30:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">90,510: The number of passengers screened nationwide by TSA on April 12. On the same day of the week a year ago, TSA screened 2.4 million people. https://t.co/Byhi8x0yJ4</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 05:00:13</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">A study showed that analysts who share a name with a CEO will make more accurate earnings forecasts for that company  https://t.co/FtyCIvzVmr</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 04:30:08</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">March was a bad month for the U.S. economy and April will be worse. But how much worse? @Spencerjakab explains. #WSJWhatsNow https://t.co/rCnBzfBvtr https://t.co/OxtevW7nFL</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 04:00:01</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Americans can now track the status of their stimulus payments and provide their bank-account information to get their money faster via direct deposit, thanks to a new IRS website https://t.co/rvpA0TV4x4</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 03:45:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">From lighting to confidence, @BethDeCarbo has pro tips for video chats. #WSJWhatsNow https://t.co/rEONIYFRG8 https://t.co/8yv9jaWQdI</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 03:30:00</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Wall Street is looking at making it less likely for a marketwide trading halt to occur immediately after the opening bell https://t.co/rXdzDr968q</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 03:15:06</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The Tour de France said it would delay its start by two months, aiming to run from Aug. 29 to Sept. 20. https://t.co/y6dat2i9cE</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 03:00:12</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Before coronavirus, working from home was a joy. Then the rookies showed up. https://t.co/TUzlHf1Las</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 02:40:10</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Executives told President Trump the U.S. needed to increase virus testing before the public would be confident to return to work, say people familiar with the talks https://t.co/odhTJK60ZD</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 02:25:35</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">#WSJWhatsNow: U.S. stocks are down as investors parse bank earnings and a sharp drop in retail sales for March https://t.co/kPktv3Yxgb</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 02:15:00</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">By providing bank-account information, people can get their stimulus payments faster, through direct deposits instead of paper checks, which may take weeks or months to arrive https://t.co/S3qIBoUAfj</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 02:00:17</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Breaking: New York Gov. Cuomo to require residents to wear masks or coverings in public places starting Friday https://t.co/1WHq40XSj3</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 01:39:39</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">A small-business loan program is expected to run out of its initial $350 billion allocation as soon as today, a person familiar with the relief fund said https://t.co/uJbD61qOi9</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 01:25:57</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">China might be secretly conducting small nuclear tests despite assertions it is adhering to an international ban, according to a State Department report https://t.co/jMlx88Sa13</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 01:12:16</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Germany plans to begin reopening its economy on Monday, Chancellor Angela Merkel said, with schools to restart in phases beginning in early May https://t.co/YGxJsB7EXv</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 12:52:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Families are posting pleas on Facebook groups for patients who have recovered from Covid-19, asking them to donate plasma so that seriously ill patients can get experimental treatment https://t.co/aJMk4fTR5i</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 12:15:06</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Should you use Zoom or FaceTime to stay digitally connected? How about Houseparty? @nicnguyen offers tips for navigating the new video-chat reality. #WSJWhatsNow https://t.co/3Rg6bzqSXS</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-16 12:00:00</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Restaurant chain Ruth's Chris Steak House was among the first public companies to disclose that it received a government-backed loan to keep people on its payroll https://t.co/RxxTbo8nNs</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 11:45:02</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Security professionals say the coronavirus crisis could become a watershed moment in the history of government surveillance.  https://t.co/XsxSZHwfEu</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 11:30:03</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Apple announces second-generation iPhone SE with a $399 starting price to reach more buyers https://t.co/2MUpKeNi0D</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 11:12:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">From @WSJopinion: Sweden, with a population similar to New York City, offers a case study of how one size does not fit all in the coronavirus epidemic, writes Holman W. Jenkins Jr. https://t.co/YhunughS4u</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 10:45:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Democrats are feeling more confidence after a liberal candidate won a state supreme court race over the conservative incumbent backed by President Trump https://t.co/DgufTHtZFc</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 10:15:09</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">South Korea's national election gives other countries early guidance on how votes might proceed once rates of new infections fall 
https://t.co/jT2PiLEGEZ</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 09:45:03</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Sen. Elizabeth Warren backed Joe Biden as the Democratic presidential candidate, becoming the last of his former top rivals to offer her endorsement https://t.co/FHg5KPkmE2</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 09:38:23</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Take a 3D look at Notre Dame's tricky restoration https://t.co/2gbloUwu8D https://t.co/rXesYtVQFq</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 09:35:59</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">One year after a devastating fire burned Paris's Notre Dame Cathedral, France's coronavirus lockdown is disrupting efforts to stabilize the landmark structure at a critical juncture https://t.co/U0AwHs8P6J</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 09:30:12</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Retail sales fell 8.7% in March, the biggest drop on record, as the coronavirus prompted widespread business closures. U.S. stock futures fell more than 2%. https://t.co/hbwg3SD2zt</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 09:08:12</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">CVS is taking on the most ambitious hiring drive in its history, partnering with Gap, Hilton and Delta Air Lines to employ their laid-off workers https://t.co/6fOlCp8J0T</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 08:45:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Even before the coronavirus pandemic, people were finding it harder to save money. That has made the shutdowns more painful. https://t.co/VDCaFo75ae</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 08:15:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The Wall Street bank reported a quarterly profit of $1.21 billion, down from $2.25 billion a year ago https://t.co/NMS9TsgkYE</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 07:40:45</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The federal government is pouring hundreds of billions of dollars into saving small businesses, but for companies like MoviE-Town Cinemas and Little Kahunas Pet Resort, the effort is falling short https://t.co/3tcMwYODGS</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 07:30:12</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The bank, the second largest in the U.S. by assets, set aside an additional $3.6 billion for potential bad loans, a reflection of the darkening economic outlook https://t.co/Ll8Gp3AzUX</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 07:13:30</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Rep. Justin Amash has hinted that he is weighing a 2020 presidential bid. One option for the Republican-turned-independent would be to seek the support of the Libertarian Party. https://t.co/UE9QpZefYO</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 06:45:03</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The total number of confirmed infections across 185 countries and regions world-wide topped 1.98 million, with more than 126,600 deaths https://t.co/F7zfjfjFiF</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 06:30:09</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">South Korea politics look different when candidates in face masks are instructed to stay out of reach of supporters https://t.co/AHivuyHnU9</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 06:00:14</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Low-income countries, seeking delays or forgiveness on their debt obligations as they face the threat of defaults, are likely to find private bondholders hard to negotiate with, according to investors https://t.co/bfIiWwRHQ1</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 05:45:02</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Take an early look at the front page of The Wall Street Journal https://t.co/73fETdUS7y https://t.co/rKIvWN4BK9</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 05:30:08</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Auto thefts in New York City are up by more than half since the coronavirus struck https://t.co/kvlE064W2Q</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 05:18:01</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Global oil demand is expected to fall by a record 9.3 million barrels a day this year as government-implemented lockdowns keep the economy at a near standstill https://t.co/WCkiItwMx3</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 05:05:42</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Heard on the Street: Japanese tech investor SoftBank has thrown money at startups like WeWork and Uber, but that approach is fast running out of road https://t.co/6RM8alzW07</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 04:45:09</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Heard on the Street: Paradoxically, the Fed's success holds the key for further rallies in the price of gold https://t.co/DXEJNLocKD</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 04:30:10</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">From @WSJopinion: Medical schools often spend more time teaching social justice than training students how to respond to a pandemic, writes Dr. Stanley Goldfarb https://t.co/4X0kZTTpqA</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 03:30:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Figures show deaths linked to the coronavirus in the U.K. have far exceeded preliminary estimates, a discrepancy that risks clouding judgments on when the outbreak has peaked and when restrictions can be eased https://t.co/bcdzBcic3v</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 03:00:11</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The home-sharing company faces escalating losses as the pandemic devastates global travel industry https://t.co/yI9jVscde3</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 02:30:12</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The Justice Department said state and local coronavirus restrictions can't treat churches less favorably than other institutions, filing legal papers in support of Mississippi churchgoers who received citations last week https://t.co/2ZOJkiS4Ff</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 02:00:11</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">From @WSJopinion: Network news is doing a better job than cable in capturing what "the real America" is doing to weather the coronavirus, writes Stephen G. Smith https://t.co/Vh21M1ZS6h</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 01:30:04</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Take an early look at the front page of The Wall Street Journal https://t.co/47GcuRem3x https://t.co/Oc3lsEqL21</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 01:00:12</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">McDonald's has asked the owners of its U.S. restaurants to do more to protect workers from the coronavirus. Franchisees, in turn, say they want more financial relief from the company to help keep them afloat. https://t.co/VXmiRHye3s</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 12:20:02</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">This high-school junior is coaching pro drivers on how to race their cars virtually https://t.co/f7Mv7f6aTC</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 12:00:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">5G is just getting started, but the next generation of wireless technology is already on the drawing board https://t.co/wcq15S7Nl5</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 11:00:09</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The metrics that NFL teams use to evaluate prospects have been mostly stagnant for decades. A new startup could be the tip of a revolution for evaluating players. https://t.co/1KsTL7JJDG</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 10:45:03</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Some find getting dressed when working from home to be essential, while others are leaning into the pajama game https://t.co/qhBz92hEre</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 09:45:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Heard on the Street: Food deliverers such as Grubhub are dependent on the health of ailing restaurants https://t.co/A8heo5fPMt</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 09:30:09</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Telemedicine company Teladoc said its remote medical appointments have more than doubled in number since early March, a sign the coronavirus pandemic is remaking how doctors take care of patients https://t.co/Za2CgTz9ON</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 09:15:04</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Amazon denies allegations by terminated workers that it has targeted employees who have protested warehouse conditions https://t.co/0hGfrK6aOK</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 09:00:03</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Relying on indoor footwear is not a novel concept, but the idea of maintaining a dedicated pair of house shoes resonates differently today https://t.co/sUq8djRH2K</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 08:30:11</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Hospitals, working to conserve space for people with severe cases of Covid-19, are using advanced forms of remote monitoring, including  AI, that make it easier to treat patients with milder symptoms in their homes https://t.co/g3pA9L0h6p</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 08:00:19</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Here are answers to questions employers and employees are asking about how new coronavirus rules expanding paid sick and family leave apply to them https://t.co/pChbdUz6CB</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 07:45:03</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">A political battle over voting by mail is building, as Democrats push for the option to reduce public gatherings in response to the coronavirus pandemic and President Trump vocally opposes such a shift in election practices https://t.co/jsIN9fo253</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 07:30:04</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Breaking: Trump says the U.S. will halt funding to the World Health Organization while the administration reviews how the group managed the coronavirus https://t.co/c1gCK5c8NW</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 07:05:53</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">A group representing campaign workers, pollsters and media advisers is suing the Small Business Administration for barring their industry from access to its coronavirus loans https://t.co/4OjulqBmaN</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 06:45:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">A brewing showdown between President Trump and governors is setting the stage for a clash between federal authority and state authority unseen in modern times https://t.co/bzTuNhw1Dy</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 06:00:12</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">How many students are attending school virtually each day? Coronavirus is making it hard to tell. https://t.co/nvQKPGa690 https://t.co/KKbXIl4qjZ</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 05:44:40</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">? Listen: In today's episode of The Journal podcast, New Jersey Gov. Phil Murphy talks about the group of seven northeastern governors working together to coordinate when their states will reopen https://t.co/9FuuSPoUdj</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 05:15:08</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Breaking: Big airlines reach agreement in principle with U.S. government on financial assistance aimed at preventing layoffs, people familiar with matter say https://t.co/eOcjGrA2TJ</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 05:07:18</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The economy has almost certainly entered a recession affecting most of the world, with a severity unmatched by anything except for the Great Depression, the IMF said https://t.co/TK5W6r4JAF https://t.co/YWSrkZv6b0</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 05:00:16</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Prison authorities say they prioritize early release of nonviolent inmates with health problems as coronavirus sweeps through lockups  https://t.co/DESFSav82g</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 04:30:06</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">From @WSJopinion: As American business rises to the occasion to take on the coronavirus, all Bernie Sanders can see is corporate greed, writes @wjmcgurn https://t.co/GKhYrhbqTb</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 04:02:09</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Can your employer take your temperature? @ChipCutter reports. #WSJWhatsNow https://t.co/D7H6Q2IWN5 https://t.co/se0GRoOsNH</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 03:32:00</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">With the pandemic sapping oil demand, the industry in Texas is debating an historic cut in output to help stabilize the market for crude https://t.co/IoxtpqjVJ9</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 03:15:04</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">JPMorgan Chase and Wells Fargo set aside billions of additional dollars to get ready for a flood of customers to default on their loans as the coronavirus pandemic pummels the economy https://t.co/pgqcKYu6u8</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 03:00:13</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Boeing said it removed more than 300 jetliners from its order book in March as airlines start to adjust their fleets amid the coronavirus pandemic https://t.co/v8858REpxv</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 02:30:15</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">#WSJWhatsNow: U.S. stocks are up as investors look ahead to the eventual reopening of the economy https://t.co/IqHhtsZTG5</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 02:15:00</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Cruise workers stranded by the coronavirus pandemic could receive little more than room and board for their time on the ship https://t.co/irhJy8O7Ge</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 01:45:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">China is taking steps to contain a new outbreak of coronavirus in communities along its northern border with Russia  https://t.co/aN4ngPAf2R</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 01:29:02</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">From @WSJopinion: The public wants to go back to work, but it wants to know how to do so safely. President Trump and the governors can both get credit if they do it the right way. https://t.co/pakaJJyfpp</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 01:15:03</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">How much is that triceratops skull on Ebay? We investigate the commercial fossil market https://t.co/T7JOCLQPYz</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 12:30:12</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Is exercise the only thing keeping you sane during shelter-in-place? @JasonGay on the at-home fitness revolution: https://t.co/mrQAyJ3fxT</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 12:15:06</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Eileen Fisher talks to @VeronicaDagher about why she decided against taking the company public #WSJWhatsNow https://t.co/WEexSNaci1</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-15 12:00:01</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">With IndyCar and Nascar shifting to iRacing simulated competition amid the pandemic, a high-school junior is giving tips to professional racers https://t.co/0NsfmEQQ90</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 11:45:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The coronavirus is hurting the co-working industry. WeWork, already under pressure to cut costs before the virus hit, is renegotiating leases and laid off more staff last week.  https://t.co/MQo4gn9Qr8</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 11:30:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">As coronavirus lockdowns crush revenue, some owners are getting creative in transforming their companies https://t.co/COue8S6Rbv</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 11:00:12</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Former President Barack Obama will endorse Joe Biden for president in a video Tuesday, according to a person familiar with the plan https://t.co/lrb19K0WmB</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 10:26:27</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">From @WSJopinion: As the world struggles to contain the coronavirus, China is still withholding vital information that would save lives, writes @wrmead https://t.co/EMHXPRw9q2</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 10:15:06</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Local governments are trying to make more of what they already know from incoming 911 calls and stitch together disparate data sets to get citywide views of the pandemic https://t.co/vn30Hzq5WL</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 10:00:17</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The economy has almost certainly entered a recession affecting most of the world, with a severity unmatched by anything except for the Great Depression, the IMF said https://t.co/GoDLGcn4NC https://t.co/vkGF4o50dE</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 09:45:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">More than 16,000 inmates are being released or diverted from jails and prisons as coronavirus spreads, according to a UCLA project. That's less than 1% of the 2.2 million people behind bars in the U.S. https://t.co/Hl5vsMHcnt</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 08:45:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">JPMorgan's first-quarter profit tumbles as the bank sets aside $6.8 billion to cover potential losses on loans amid the coronavirus shutdown https://t.co/TPPPVdj8xi</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 07:17:02</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Johnson &amp; Johnson posted net income of $5.8 billion for the first quarter as the coronavirus drove demand for over-the-counter medicine such as Tylenol https://t.co/oLj7zano45</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 07:15:12</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">For Renault, the onset of the coronavirus epidemic snuffed out its bid to become a mainstream brand in China https://t.co/hWDKded32e</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 06:54:03</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Heard on the Street: Food deliverers such as Grubhub are dependent on the health of ailing restaurants https://t.co/iRBcImXOg9</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 06:15:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">U.S. airlines have mortgaged gates, flight paths and just about any asset they could find in the back of a hangar to weather the coronavirus crisis. Now, they are considering selling miles in bulk to their credit-card partners to raise cash. https://t.co/NIsQRqg0mw</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 05:45:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Take an early look at the front page of The Wall Street Journal https://t.co/4NrwZ8R6pX https://t.co/0HxzyJGdSr</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 05:15:04</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Confirmed cases of Covid-19, the disease caused by the coronavirus, passed 1.92 million world-wide, more than a quarter of them in the U.S. https://t.co/uo402GXaJS</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 05:00:03</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">France and Italy prolong their nationwide curbs as officials urge residents to stay the course, saying data show that restrictions are working https://t.co/tQvftAp9P5</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 04:45:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The XFL was in the middle of a promising reboot season before canceling its games because of coronavirus https://t.co/4ESv2PtDWK</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 04:30:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Chinese businesses are bouncing back, but the pandemic has depressed economic activity and consumer demand in key Western markets https://t.co/7iCGaT4yUS</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 04:16:04</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Republican orthodoxy has changed since the 2008-09 rescue, and coronavirus rescue plans show the party changing again, with big-government solutions https://t.co/KJANBp76bf</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 04:00:14</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Vaccination drives for polio, measles and other diseases are paused, raising fears that other epidemics could surge in the poorest nations https://t.co/SDLLcSaGFx</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 03:30:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Three states and New York City asked the Supreme Court to block regulations that penalize immigrants for seeking public benefits, arguing it could exacerbate the coronavirus crisis https://t.co/Z6npP6YQAR</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 02:30:10</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">North Korea fires short-range missiles in its fifth weapons test of the year https://t.co/6Jlcg1Xrxa</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 02:17:33</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">New York City officials have asked local groups for rain ponchos to be used as medical gowns as Mayor Bill de Blasio said some protective equipment would be in short supply https://t.co/wuh7H5vaV4</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 02:00:03</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">A reporter weighs risk, family and career as her physician husband heads to work https://t.co/NEsxrhylEX</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 01:30:08</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Investors in mainland Chinese stocks shrugged off data showing first-quarter exports fell by 11% year over year https://t.co/lljxlHDk4w</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 01:00:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Take an early look at the front page of The Wall Street Journal https://t.co/VhUOQnSIVB https://t.co/v57XCMdJfH</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 12:40:04</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Would you buy a Coronavirus T-shirt? https://t.co/4avRcZtd8s</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 12:30:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">As New York City asked residents to stay home, wealthy New Yorkers descended on the Hamptons to shelter in place, disrupting life of local year-round residents https://t.co/9ESf3zkkwJ</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 12:00:13</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">A federal appeals court late Monday eased a Texas ban on abortion during the coronavirus, a move that may save the Supreme Court from having to weigh in right now https://t.co/vbNTx8zNOg</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 11:22:38</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Temperature checks at airports. Plexiglass shields. Mandatory face masks. The "Six-Foot Office." What American CEOs are thinking. https://t.co/01dScvtz7m</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 10:30:08</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Congressional leaders and the White House stalled in efforts to break an impasse over the size and shape of the next package of aid responding to the coronavirus pandemic https://t.co/HzoO7JnatM</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 10:00:12</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">From @WSJopinion: Newly declassified documents show that the FBI knew some of its evidence against the Trump campaign likely came from Russian disinformation, writes @SenRonJohnson https://t.co/p5IfoJx0aU</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 08:30:10</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Owners of drive-in theaters in New York seek to reopen during the coronavirus pandemic, saying they provide a socially-distant respite https://t.co/JOvS7MWHZT</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 08:15:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Virtual dog yoga and comedy nights: Pet owners are trying digital means to entertain themselves and their four-legged friends as stay-at-home orders continue https://t.co/jlBuYEzmg1</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 08:00:16</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The IRS has extended the deadline for filing individual tax returns for 2019 to July 15 from April 15. Here's what you need to know.
https://t.co/RoFpTbWQt2</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 07:50:02</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Joe Biden wins last week's Democratic presidential primary in Wisconsin in an election that highlighted the challenges in voting amid the coronavirus pandemic https://t.co/txg2Xz2PUt</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 07:15:11</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">New Orleans and the surrounding region are facing some of the highest Covid-19 infection and fatality rates in the country. Doctors and health experts explain what may be contributing to the outbreak. #WSJWhatsNow https://t.co/fCOREC4cmK</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 07:00:00</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">About 2 million homeowners are skipping their monthly mortgage payments, according to new industry data, a number that is forecast to rise further as more Americans lose their jobs due to the coronavirus pandemic https://t.co/xtSWpYefX7</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 06:45:06</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">? Listen: In today's episode of The Journal podcast, @samschech explains how Apple and Google are working together to try to turn billions of smartphones into coronavirus trackers, and what it shows about the trade-offs between privacy and public health https://t.co/vpnQQnHUoC</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 06:30:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Some plans to reopen the economy sound like science fiction. Get used to it. https://t.co/nkbA47dJFu</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 06:20:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">From @WSJopinion: The coronavirus crisis reminds us how delicate wealth, health and enjoyment are. Stop attacking the culture that creates and sustains them, writes @andykessler https://t.co/goiGu41iYv</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 06:00:24</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">African nationals in the Chinese city of Guangzhou say they have been have been barred from hotels and restaurants under the city's coronavirus measures https://t.co/BneMwTRRNb</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 05:45:02</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Warehouse developers expect the coronavirus-driven upheaval in supply chains will trigger long-term growth in demand for industrial real estate https://t.co/qmey73H1EP</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 05:15:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The Trump administration is considering withholding funds from WHO in part to pressure the group to hire more Americans https://t.co/1SyIsjTOFa</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 05:00:11</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Parts maker Pace Industries has filed for bankruptcy, saying the pandemic has disrupted its supply chain and forced it to close plants and lay off most employees https://t.co/5JQr19gcVQ</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 04:30:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Stephon Marbury saw what the coronavirus had done to China. So the former NBA star-turned-Chinese sports hero emailed NBA commissioner Adam Silver to warn the league. https://t.co/HFpvQ0YNay</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 04:00:17</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Multiple offers. Bidding wars. All-cash deals hours after listings go live: Welcome to Seattle, the city that four weeks ago was considered an epicenter of the coronavirus pandemic. https://t.co/Y2CXY5DV97</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 03:45:10</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Looking for in-demand items like hand sanitizer and face masks? @nicnguyen has these tips. #WSJWhatsNow https://t.co/Wy2nlZDD4t https://t.co/DyWoKKrPvm</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 03:30:00</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Netflix, Disney+ or HBO MAX? An essential guide through 26 on-demand services and the shows and movies they offer as well as their costs and bundle options. https://t.co/2sFLGYZg3S</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 02:30:08</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Sen. Bernie Sanders endorsed Joe Biden, saying "we've got to make Trump a one-term president." https://t.co/sA86DjMFk1</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 02:20:19</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">CEOs are thinking about getting back to business, and the new normal will be really weird https://t.co/GaOgUUcO0c</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 02:15:09</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">At least 19 people died when tornadoes and severe thunderstorms tore across several Southern states Sunday and early Monday https://t.co/UHOqYk6MwH</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 02:00:14</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">#WSJWhatsNow: The S&amp;P 500 is down as investors look ahead to the start of the corporate earnings season https://t.co/WT3pmYsvgO</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 01:45:00</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Among the many unknowns about the new coronavirus, researchers are hunting for an answer to a particularly knotty question: Do warmer temperatures slow the spread? https://t.co/PcCktGVHPP</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 01:30:06</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Anthony Scaramucci is facing one of his biggest tests as SkyBridge struggles with the poor performance of its hedge-fund managers https://t.co/Fd28OYziRF</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 01:15:09</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Amazon will allow third-party sellers to ship nonessential items again, a sign it is ramping up to meet consumer needs, say people familiar with the matter https://t.co/8OU51CZncl</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 12:45:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Social media has helped connect people during the coronavirus crisis. But as health authorities tighten their guidelines, platforms including Facebook and Nextdoor also are turning into places for complaints for people those not following the rules. https://t.co/CRDYIb2tjZ</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 12:30:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Heard on the Street: Microsoft boasts about the video-calling ability of its Teams platform just as the Zoom looks vulnerable https://t.co/qOOGw0fXWK</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 12:15:11</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Singer-songwriter Imogen Heap shares advice for up-and-coming musicians #WSJWhatsNow https://t.co/glzAPzzY7g</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-14 12:00:01</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">President Trump said a coalition of 23 nations that reached a deal on Sunday to address a mounting global oil glut is aiming to cut production by 20 million barrels of oil a day, more than twice the number originally revealed https://t.co/7j6fNP6U5P</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 11:45:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">States are looking for alternatives to traditional primaries and caucuses so they can avoid asking voters to gather in public places, wait in lines, touch shared equipment and interact with poll workers https://t.co/KRfUpVjHT7</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 11:15:06</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Amazon said it plans to hire 75,000 additional workers, the latest move by the company to staff up as the coronavirus pandemic pushes consumers to buy more products online https://t.co/U3IgV9sLGK</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 10:53:49</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">U.S. airlines are burning through cash. Selling miles to their credit-card partners could be their next move. https://t.co/tQZokkZLmE</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 10:45:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Stephon Marbury saw what the coronavirus had done to China. So the former NBA star-turned Chinese sports hero emailed NBA commissioner Adam Silver to warn the league. https://t.co/q85TJjhXmb</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 10:15:10</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Is exercise the only thing keeping you sane? @JasonGay on the at-home fitness revolution: https://t.co/F2HieF9MQv</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 10:00:16</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Breaking: A sailor from the USS Theodore Roosevelt died from complications related to Covid-19, the first death of a crew member from the aircraft carrier https://t.co/xbjcdaJVFB</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 09:26:37</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Dr. Fauci, regarded as the voice of reason in the coronavirus task force, said the U.S. could have saved more lives if it had moved faster on social distancing https://t.co/57h50SF441</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 09:10:03</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">When the classroom is Zoom, lesson plans require constant toggling and new ways of reading the room https://t.co/nVwKMFE7Gc</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 08:30:09</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">23 countries reach a historic deal to cut oil output, airlines find aid terms hard to swallow and millions of Christians celebrate Easter in isolation #WSJWhatsNow https://t.co/BwbBpbCNGn</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 08:13:42</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">A by-the-numbers look at the economic toll of coronavirus in terms of dividends cut, buybacks scrapped and workers furloughed https://t.co/B8y9VZ2bLx</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 08:00:08</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Concerns rise that easing lockdowns could spur new outbreaks of the coronavirus that has claimed more than 114,000 lives globally https://t.co/CzxFX6iKsz</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 07:45:02</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Blackstone is investing $2 billion in Alnylam Pharmaceuticals, giving the biotech firm the cash it needs to bring more drugs to market https://t.co/DGZzN4REe4</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 07:15:04</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Zoos around the U.S. have applied for federal loans and posted videos of animals to encourage donations. Coronavirus-related closures have slashed revenue during what is usually the busiest time of year. #WSJWhatsNow https://t.co/ZwpvhuRADI</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 07:00:00</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The International Monetary Fund anticipates the worst economic fallout since the Great Depression from the coronavirus pandemic https://t.co/fE16E752KC</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 06:45:02</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Buyout volumes, already sluggish before the pandemic, have come to a virtual standstill and any hopes of selling investments profitably are gone for now https://t.co/4QYSGl2Aih</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 06:00:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Take an early look at the front page of The Wall Street Journal https://t.co/RlNCvkL4Eh https://t.co/2uxxsVwwWe</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 05:15:04</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The Centers for Medicare and Medicaid Services is expected to take action to make elder care facilities share more information about coronavirus cases with residents, staff and family members https://t.co/aWU3mFqgkg</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 03:00:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Congo could face a triple emergency as authorities deal with lingering cases of Ebola, a surge in coronavirus and instability that has racked the country for more than a decade https://t.co/fzDdQKElMw</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 02:30:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Take an early look at the front page of The Wall Street Journal https://t.co/mXk5xiFGrZ https://t.co/woQK97Ycgq</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 01:35:03</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Stocks fall as investors digest oil deal https://t.co/gNEoiJurMK</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 01:15:28</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The nation is watching how New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo is handling the coronavirus outbreak, and it likes what it sees https://t.co/kL8G1W9ZhK</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 01:00:08</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The $2 trillion stimulus package passed last month included everything the airline industry requested, and some restrictions they find hard to swallow https://t.co/5jSZsH17qe</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 12:30:04</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">"Not wearing masks in Hong Kong is like not wearing pants." City residents are now antivirus enforcers, from refusing service to social shaming. https://t.co/39w7lRs8w2</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 12:00:14</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The pandemic is especially destabilizing for people with depression and anxiety. But there are steps to take that can help. https://t.co/MoY1PFGCI9</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 11:30:08</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Companies are trying to find strategies beyond virtual happy hours to keep their workers feeling connected https://t.co/lxdUO1bohh</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 11:00:10</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">In Eastern and Central Europe, infections have largely been kept under control and governments are starting to loosen lockdowns https://t.co/aoPIowG2SR</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 10:30:08</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Any decision to close New York City public schools for the remainder of the academic year is premature and must be coordinated with other districts, New York Gov. Cuomo said https://t.co/kcGnOplyG6</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 09:30:06</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Companies with female directors are more likely to quickly recall dangerous products, researchers say https://t.co/uUrYhxRbxi</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 09:00:20</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Why cleaning out a closet, organizing bookshelves by color and other tips for tidying your home environment can provide a big emotional payoff https://t.co/TV1wWFraaY</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 08:00:15</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Cuomo for president? The New York governor says no, but speculation persists. https://t.co/woyhcjctlw</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 07:30:08</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">"Scones in the living room? Over!" Walkie-talkies have won a following among people stuck at home https://t.co/5koGSabT72</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 07:15:04</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Pitchers need to keep throwing to remain fresh when the baseball season begins https://t.co/YD332DACCk</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 06:30:03</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Anthony Fauci and Deborah Birx belong to a generation of physicians whose professional lives are bookended by two lethal viruses. This is what the infectious disease leaders who came of age in the 1980s know now. https://t.co/aBpkgWIYIa</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 05:45:10</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Tempted by plummeting airfares and hotel rates, some travelers are hunting for half-price holidays later in the year https://t.co/SyzDxXO8rl</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 05:30:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Ford and GM assembly-line workers trade power tools for tweezers to mass-produce ventilators. Will they arrive in time to save lives? https://t.co/22t1Jlo27a</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 04:00:09</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Apple, Facebook and other tech giants are still in the market for tens of thousands of new hires https://t.co/lASt5KIkJY</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 03:45:03</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">From @WSJopinion: The Trump administration has failed to convey an impression of strong international leadership during the coronavirus crisis, writes Robert B. Zoellick https://t.co/XsQLP3GQpW</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 03:30:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">What are your life hacks for weathering the pandemic? Read our advice and submit your own tips in the story featured here: https://t.co/qsLaOT6KbY</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 02:45:10</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">If you want to help seniors get groceries during the coronavirus pandemic, here are some resources, courtesy of @juliejargon #WSJWhatsNow https://t.co/vimgB7UKk7 https://t.co/8rhUtQ1gIY</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 02:30:00</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">As events like SXSW and Coachella were canceled or postponed due to the pandemic, Airbnb hosts saw bookings shrink and revenue disappear https://t.co/KE9Q7gAdxz</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 02:15:04</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Breaking: The U.S., Saudi Arabia and Russia have agreed to lead an unprecedented agreement to help reverse an oil-price rout https://t.co/8bKycawD3J</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 02:03:36</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Cardiovascular disease is the most common and deadliest so far of the underlying conditions that make people more vulnerable to the ravages of Covid-19 https://t.co/fTUwGJ9OLU</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 01:45:03</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Hospitals, grocery stores and other essential services are enlisting robots in the fight against coronavirus https://t.co/deHFyZkIWl</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 01:30:15</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Tackling wills, life insurance and trusts doesn't have to involve a trip to the lawyer https://t.co/JnSW75PvDa</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 01:15:06</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">"Scones in the living room? Over!" Walkie-talkies have won a following among people stuck at home https://t.co/ITnO46p2XW</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 12:45:08</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Watch: For many around the world, coronavirus lockdowns and social-distancing measures mean financial hardship. As some are growing desperate, governments are addressing the risks of social unrest. https://t.co/Roel6c3kTv</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 12:15:01</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Coronavirus victims are dying alone, separated from loved ones in their final moments. "I can't even be there to say anything," said David "Michael" Dudley Jr., who told his dying 61-year-old father goodbye on a videoconference call. https://t.co/yGhYTYvtxH</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-13 12:00:17</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Some school districts are halting meal deliveries, and turning to pickups and alternative arrangements, due to worries about spreading the coronavirus https://t.co/u7yxHSOI1Q</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-12 11:03:02</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Coronavirus. Spring flooding. And still ahead, the hurricane season. Cities along the Mississippi River face challenges on multiple fronts. https://t.co/BED3cnYorb</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-12 10:45:21</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Airlines are consumed with new work in the coronavirus era: navigating government bailouts, negotiating with unions and scrounging for business like flying cargo https://t.co/so2V5bsQXB</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-12 10:15:02</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">One of the youngest CEOs in the U.S. oil patch wants Texas to mandate lower production as the coronavirus hits crude prices https://t.co/mWCrzq3WLQ</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-12 09:45:08</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">People walk up to a shed where a priest hears their confession. A boom box playing Gregorian chants provides some privacy. https://t.co/TDMao8cpCO</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-12 09:30:13</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">China shut down domestic wild-animal traders on fears their goods sparked the coronavirus pandemic. Now officials are offering tax breaks to export products like edible reptiles, civet musk and rhino horn overseas. https://t.co/amNS9Vljhr</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-12 09:00:12</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Breaking: U.K. Prime Minister Boris Johnson was discharged from a hospital after being treated for coronavirus. He will not immediately return to work. https://t.co/GSry1SGZw1</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-12 08:52:28</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The coronavirus pandemic has prompted sports bodies that usually generate much of their own revenue to seek help https://t.co/zRYqmp2XI5</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-12 08:30:09</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Cardiovascular disease is the most common and deadliest so far of the underlying conditions that make people more vulnerable to the ravages of Covid-19 https://t.co/zcInPB55pF</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-12 08:00:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Administration officials have said the $350 billion small-business support plan approved in late March could run out of money this week https://t.co/kMh15p2WNg</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-12 07:45:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">From @WSJopinion: China broke the World Health Organization. The U.S. has to fix it or leave and start its own group, writes @lanheechen https://t.co/Jmm6vlG1xa</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-12 07:30:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">U.S. companies have filed dozens of requests for tariff relief for products in short supply that are needed to fight the coronavirus pandemic https://t.co/jLi9w8cv8c</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-12 07:00:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Churches held Easter services with few or no parishioners, though many livestreamed their services online and some were televised https://t.co/TPNWIl2YH5</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-12 04:30:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">More than half of India is involved one way or another in the growing, delivering and selling of food, economists say. It's all coming to a standstill in the world's biggest coronavirus lockdown. https://t.co/O0HKO8ZK5Q</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-12 04:00:03</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Beyond acute stress and anxiety, psychologists say coronavirus-related confinement is beginning to trigger deeper troubles, including depression and compulsive disorders https://t.co/munkjPSWtG</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-12 03:00:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Beijing helps foreign enterprises resolve supply-chain bottlenecks and restart production to fend off the slowdown caused by the coronavirus https://t.co/Nl1zNse3fB</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-12 02:00:10</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">For his detractors, Cardinal Pell is a symbol of the abuse crisis. To his supporters, he is a scapegoat that was targeted by enemies of the church. https://t.co/Oxgo4XKaxc</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-12 01:00:12</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Joe Biden won the Democratic primary in Alaska, which voted entirely by mail due to the coronavirus https://t.co/ji8i1RqC8V</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-12 11:23:14</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">After releasing two records in three years, the Strokes put out just three in the next decade and a half. What happened? https://t.co/FAe9IYt7g4</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-12 10:30:08</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Scientists hope gene variations will explain why some younger, healthy Covid-19 patients require serious medical intervention or die from the infection https://t.co/rA0y2WAE6V</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-12 10:00:10</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Lonely and bored as you wait out the pandemic? Play classic board games online with family and friends. https://t.co/LNw3MR02XZ</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-12 09:40:03</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Abortion providers asked the Supreme Court to relax a Texas executive order that bans nearly all abortions during the public-health crisis created by the coronavirus https://t.co/XEq6IPzJm1</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-12 09:20:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Coronavirus closures choked off revenues at zoos during a peak period for visitors. But animal care must continue, and zoo keepers are seeking loans and donations. https://t.co/uimxVDx7FX</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-12 08:14:01</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Democratic presidential candidate Joe Biden faces a six-month obstacle course made exceedingly more complicated by the global coronavirus pandemic https://t.co/zc9P9gXMce</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-12 07:45:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">A French doctor has emerged as a standard-bearer for those who support the use of hydroxycholoroquine as treatment for the new coronavirus, despite a lack of evidence that it is effective https://t.co/MxOkbYBNnv</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-12 07:16:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Essay: There are ways to make this period of self-quarantine not only endurable but rewarding https://t.co/19KuQ7b8Yy</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-12 07:02:01</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Major studios are rushing new releases to streaming services while movie houses remain closed across the country. The experiment could spell changes to how you watch films even after the theaters reopen. https://t.co/nnkKjeB6Re</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-12 06:15:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Government monitoring authorities in France have seen a jump in reports of serious side effects from hydroxychloroquine used to treat patients with Covid-19 https://t.co/oUDzOwKgcK</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-12 05:15:04</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">GM is making 30,000 ventilators for the national stockpile, of which about 6,000 would be delivered by June https://t.co/g6aTcgtpM3</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-12 04:30:09</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">From @WSJopinion: Joe Biden offers the backward-looking vision of an exhausted liberalism, writes Barton Swaim https://t.co/CqEgAbFPL8</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-12 03:30:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The new coronavirus has hit more than 2,100 nursing homes and other senior facilities around the U.S., killing over 2,300 people, according to a survey by The Wall Street Journal https://t.co/5VQQt4fY2Q</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-12 03:16:02</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Do your children need a break from online school? @juliejargon has a couple of resources for digital fun. #WSJWhatsNow https://t.co/y6Aa0lvURr https://t.co/q0fhLd4QUx</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-12 02:30:00</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">How the coronavirus crisis has changed life for Sam Harshbarger, a 32-year-old stocker at a Kroger store in Huntington, https://t.co/gjBdG9AQVO. https://t.co/FlgzST2vP8</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-12 01:45:08</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Despite a staggering death toll, there were signs that measures to curtail spread of the new coronavirus are working https://t.co/DazUwkJ7cA</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-12 01:15:06</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">New data provide the first hard look at how many Americans are struggling to make rent during the coronavirus pandemic https://t.co/GYkHyYMkDN</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-12 01:00:15</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Breaking: The U.S. became the country with the most reported coronavirus deaths, surpassing Italy, with 18,860 https://t.co/CCSTi90xOv</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-12 12:19:51</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Americans who stocked up on rolls in the coronavirus lockdown are willing to make trades https://t.co/79USViQFD8</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-12 12:00:03</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">As lockdowns move from days to weeks, frustrated people are interpreting government rules in ways that allow them more time outside https://t.co/wMd1miU2cD</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 11:00:13</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">In New York, emergency rooms are overcrowded. Refrigerated trucks house dead bodies in the street. In California, hospital beds sit empty and the state recently lent 500 ventilators to harder-hit states. https://t.co/VGH8i12KDB</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 10:14:06</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Breaking: New York City's public school system, the largest in the country, will remain closed for the rest of the school year as the city continues to slow the spread of the novel coronavirus https://t.co/G99JNX9bAY</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 10:04:34</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Deliveries are safer during the coronavirus pandemic, but a store run may be unavoidable. Here are the precautions to take. https://t.co/TfgnIN2xWb</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 10:00:19</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">A small group that was given an experimental Gilead treatment showed improvement, but clinical trials are needed to assess its effectiveness https://t.co/JLebjPm6Sj</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 09:45:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Governors are frustrated that rapid coronavirus tests distributed by the Trump administration are largely unusable due to supply shortages https://t.co/I7q6olziR3</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 09:30:11</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">"If this goes on like this, Europe will collapse." The pandemic is threatening the viability of the entire European Union. https://t.co/PZVaekQEQm</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 09:14:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Millions of Americans are entering old age saddled with mortgages. The burden will likely get heavier as the coronavirus pandemic batters the economy.  https://t.co/sfMHAQ5mgB</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 09:00:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Corporations world-wide have moved fast in the fight against coronavirus. Why are so many of them flat-footed in ordinary times? https://t.co/ByWx87yMQ3</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 06:39:26</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Some empty-nest parents turn their children's bedrooms into home offices and gyms. But what happens when the kids return to shelter in place? https://t.co/lgfhrW9XY4</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 06:00:04</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Take a look at the front page of today's Wall Street Journal https://t.co/8ballNMTXi https://t.co/FudaMXViwO</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 05:30:08</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The presidential race this week became, indisputably, a contest between Donald Trump and Joe Biden, two children of the 1940s whose paths diverged markedly on their way to this moment https://t.co/DT8C9yrlY5</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 01:30:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Why more movies are being produced with the living room, and not the multiplex, in mind https://t.co/XTsX5mpt4A</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 01:00:13</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The Trump administration threatened to withhold visas from several Central American countries if they refuse to accept their citizens deported from the U.S. during the coronavirus pandemic https://t.co/17yyF0qsyn</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 12:45:03</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Here's an early look at the front page of The Wall Street Journal's weekend edition https://t.co/T7Nu9fHvCy https://t.co/VYDxXFQrt5</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 12:30:08</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The U.S. has passed 500,000 confirmed coronavirus cases, according to data compiled by Johns Hopkins University https://t.co/lxpaIAR3Mn</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 11:25:26</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Mobile banking startup Current says it has already credited about 10,000 accounts, as the first batch of coronavirus stimulus payments is sent by the U.S. government on Friday https://t.co/hTmvXzFydS</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 11:00:15</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">A judge approved the offer from Patrick Soon-Shiong, the owner of the Los Angeles Times, to buy a closed hospital and reopen it to treat coronavirus patients https://t.co/gJrcnIC21M</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 10:30:08</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Are temporarily clear skies a glimpse of America's electric-car future? https://t.co/lfnSHXkika</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 10:00:08</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Stuck at home and unable to visit bars and restaurants amid coronavirus shutdowns, Americans are buying booze. Lots of it. https://t.co/2tXZZKRxy0</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 09:15:06</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Tech giants Apple and Google will partner to build software that would alert people if they were in contact with someone infected with the coronavirus https://t.co/VqgyDgjRED</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 09:00:08</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">New blood tests could indicate how widely the virus has spread and who has developed some protection against infection, but key unknowns remain https://t.co/Zl0JDDcm8U</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 08:45:06</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The coronavirus pandemic has deepened long-running tensions between hardest-hit southern European nations and the financially stronger north. Whether and how this clash gets resolved is likely to determine the long-term viability of the entire EU. https://t.co/piQ1GKjNMH</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 08:30:08</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The coronavirus crisis could give another boost to the practice of seeking connection through artificial intelligence https://t.co/7A3C9uW11Y</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 07:45:09</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Buying a new car during the coronavirus pandemic is possible with much of the process online and curbside delivery by some U.S. dealers. From deals on new cars to safely doing test drives, here are answers to common questions about auto shopping now. https://t.co/5JWM7kuoP6</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 06:45:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The coronavirus pandemic has made Zoom a household name. But @djtgallagher explains why its greatest strength is also its greatest weakness. #WSJWhatsNow https://t.co/3jkjMXT36k</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 06:17:00</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Harvey Weinstein, who is serving a 23-year sentence in New York, is facing a new sexual-assault charge in Los Angeles https://t.co/mfJnBqBddz</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 06:15:09</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Top Democrats said they hoped to reach a deal with Republicans next week on a new coronavirus aid package that has been blocked by partisan disputes https://t.co/wcrZNv0L0r</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 05:45:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The IRS is now offering a free portal for low-income people who don't typically file tax returns to claim their stimulus payments https://t.co/yTR5CyGbf9</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 05:30:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Is this the key to help restart an economy in the pandemic? Unlike many insurers world-wide, Chinese insurers are promising to cover business losses from the coronavirus. https://t.co/aIyIXvJdMp</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 05:00:03</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The demand for oil has plummeted as the coronavirus has shut down much of the world, but most producers are still pumping. In today's episode of The Journal podcast, @russellgold explains the global game of chicken inside the oil industry. 

? Listen: https://t.co/5UUxq8ELop</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 04:30:08</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Corporations world-wide have moved fast in the fight against coronavirus. Why are so many of them flat-footed in ordinary times?  https://t.co/XXXNUL2ln2</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 03:45:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Amid the pandemic, the entire act of human grief has been recalibrated, writes @jasongay https://t.co/bo1AFjIzFo</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 03:30:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The largest U.S. pilot union said flight crews need more protections to keep the aviation system functioning amid the coronavirus pandemic that has decimated demand for air travel https://t.co/ILmp5bG60Y</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 03:14:03</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">3M says Performance Supply tried to sell 3M-branded masks to New York officials for up to six times list prices  https://t.co/VfHP7efRPx</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 03:00:13</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Tips to troubleshoot your home internet connection from @ChipCutter #WJSWhatsNow https://t.co/1ZglZVrX9W https://t.co/bvaBbVT4W6</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 02:40:00</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Tech giants Apple and Google will partner to build software that would alert people if they were in contact with someone infected with the coronavirus https://t.co/y58mvvTUjm</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 02:01:19</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The Trump administration has reworked a plan to phase out federal support for drive-through testing sites, after stirring opposition from some local officials and lawmakers at a time when U.S. cases are expected to peak https://t.co/nKShWXTCBG</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 01:30:06</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">"I'm sorry I can't kiss you," Neutz's daughter, Kathy Mills, told her dying mother through tears, wearing two protective masks, safety goggles and two pairs of gloves. Days later, she said her final goodbye over video chat. https://t.co/hutYIZn4b3 https://t.co/J38z84Fq10</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 01:19:30</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Keiko Neutz had eight children, 28 grandchildren and 10 great grandchildren. But none of them were at the hospital when the 87-year-old family matriarch died of coronavirus. https://t.co/zLivlqBe9f</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 01:12:58</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">"I'll be with you every step of the way," Nancy Hopkins promised her 83-year-old father, Robert McCord, just before paramedics put him into an ambulance. That was as close as she would ever again get to him. https://t.co/CFTao8freO https://t.co/DRTHP426ET</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 01:08:12</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Coronavirus victims are dying alone, separated from loved ones in their final moments. "I can't even be there to say anything," said David "Michael" Dudley Jr., who told his dying 61-year-old father goodbye on a videoconference call. https://t.co/P4Ixykb0A5</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 01:04:40</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The coronavirus is yielding something uncommon for governors in this era of sharp political divisions: Some are winning loud applause from members of both parties for their response to the outbreak https://t.co/hhLJWRakV2</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 12:30:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Stuck at home and unable to visit bars and restaurants amid coronavirus shutdowns, Americans are buying booze. Lots of it. https://t.co/HvQQTCxg7q</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 12:15:08</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Confused about traveling right now? How to stay healthy, how to get a refund when you cancel a trip, and when it might be safe to travel again. https://t.co/sZmiGZYmEs</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-11 12:00:17</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Insurance company State Farm is slashing $2 billion of premiums owed on 40 million vehicles, offering 21 million households a financial-relief program as auto claims have plunged https://t.co/PuN8V2Vayv</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 11:45:03</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Some homeowners prefer to take the DIY approach to disinfecting, but a recent survey found that many are doing it improperly. Now many Americans are turning to professional disinfection companies for help. https://t.co/89wcQrMsGI</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 11:30:09</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Suits against the University of Miami or Drexel allege the schools are failing to give them the educational experience they paid for, one with in-person instruction. Total cost to attend either school exceeds $70,000 a year. https://t.co/sgjiAtSLWM</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 11:00:10</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">A shortage of psychiatrists and other mental-health-care providers, especially in rural areas, is in focus as the coronavirus pandemic fuels surge in calls for help https://t.co/vZqGDnZBkX</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 10:45:08</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">From @WSJopinion: "Hardship generally makes people stronger," a social psychologist observes. What will we learn? https://t.co/1Zw0r5lDUa</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 10:15:12</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">As attendance at day-care centers is down up to 90%, first responders say they are more dependent than ever on the providers that remain open https://t.co/MUVC1XfP77</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 10:00:12</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">China has tripled its presence on Facebook and Twitter in recent months, researchers say, to spread messages that can incite doubt about basic facts and sometimes promote fictitious claims https://t.co/IEZDaL6vfQ</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 09:30:14</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">As Washington and Beijing butt heads over the coronavirus, scientists and doctors in the U.S. and China have been holding virtual meetings and trading notes on how to best treat patients https://t.co/7YwRoxX9Qm</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 09:00:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">U.S. confirmed cases rose to more than 466,000, according to Johns Hopkins, though the actual number is likely higher, experts say, due to lack of widespread testing, false negatives and differences in reporting standards https://t.co/yTO4wYBgM6</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 08:36:27</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">New habits can carry us ahead in an organized way, letting us heighten our sense of control over our days and nights and keep disabling feelings in check https://t.co/YMRFmWYvxm</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 08:30:10</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Should you take advantage of those travel deals popping up online? Our travel columnist says it depends. #WSJWhatsNow https://t.co/wAo7yBgm8D</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 08:20:00</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Even as a loan program for small businesses weakened by the coronavirus pandemic expands, the first applicants still await funding https://t.co/xEMtv7uoZ4</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 08:15:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Attorney General William Barr says Michael Atkinson, who reviewed Ukraine whistleblower complaint, ignored Justice Department guidance https://t.co/qHif9x7pEE</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 08:00:11</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">New blood tests could indicate how widely the virus has spread and who has developed some protection against infection, but key unknowns remain https://t.co/qmVd4LlLAl</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 07:20:03</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Interrupted treatments, heightened anxiety and enforced isolation during the coronavirus pandemic could cause lasting damage to mental health, especially to those with existing conditions https://t.co/uGoqDo7EXu</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 06:30:09</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">A Houston billionaire is accused of using a complex web of trusts and limited liability companies to prevent his wife from accessing cash and the 13 homes they acquired together https://t.co/wpthnJURbz</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 05:30:06</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Take an early look at the front page of The Wall Street Journal https://t.co/jXY6aJER60 https://t.co/7BwXsXuURV</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 05:15:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Only 58% of Americans disinfect their homes properly. Now many are getting help. https://t.co/aiDKmDbMwA</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 05:00:04</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">For many, simply raising a glass of wine to friends arrayed across a computer screen is just the kind of virtual experience that helps soften our current reality https://t.co/4B07h9uv9b</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 04:00:10</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">When you're stressed, reliable relief comes from revisiting classic YA novels like "The Outsiders" https://t.co/gZynznb9nS</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 02:30:08</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Take an early look at the front page of The Wall Street Journal https://t.co/vVfRSJuk4E https://t.co/ayCy0YGV0k</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 02:25:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">From @WSJopinion: As President Trump confronts the coronavirus, he benefits from reforms instituted by his predecessors, Presidents Bill Clinton and George W. Bush, writes @KarlRove https://t.co/EpDa9ctz5i</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 01:30:08</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Looking for a quick pasta fix? Try this lemony version with kale that you can have on the table in 20 minutes. https://t.co/syDKYDgMfh</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 01:00:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">At a time when the luckier among us can have takeout food and booze delivered to our doorsteps, movies about delivery services may provide flavorsome accompaniment, writes @JoeMorgenstern https://t.co/k9N8RsJRum</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 12:00:06</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">In communities protected by imposing security gates and high-tech extras, security guards have come to feel like part of the family https://t.co/MSLi4bWGcq</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 11:30:17</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">You don't have to call it the new kale. Cabbage is an icon in its own right--and indispensable right now. https://t.co/j9QOvmaOwz</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 11:15:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Always wanted to be a wine nerd? No time like the present to learn how. https://t.co/ZfRMNTHBQt</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 11:00:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Boeing is considering a plan to reduce its workforce by about 10%, people familiar with the matter said, as the aerospace giant grapples with the fallout from the coronavirus pandemic https://t.co/ZpRGsUsK28</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 10:28:06</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">From @WSJopinion: The eyes of the world will soon be on Austria, which is set to begin reopening its economy over the next few weeks, writes Barbara Kolm https://t.co/IcsFyg6aWh</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 10:20:04</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">A federal judge again restrained Texas from banning abortions during the coronavirus public-health crisis, saying the state can ban some, but not all, abortions https://t.co/neIsBtccsh</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 09:40:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Nate Morris can't speak for himself right now. The 24-year-old hospital worker is in a medically induced coma due to complications from Covid-19. So his partner of four years shared his story for him. https://t.co/5CRptOBMrj https://t.co/pg87z1K5Cf</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 09:30:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The indefinite delay to the baseball season comes at a precarious moment, when Minor League Baseball was already facing the possibility of enormous disruption https://t.co/LF4jTaMvyo</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 08:45:06</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">One sure outcome of the coronavirus crisis: Government, businesses and some households will be loaded with mountains of additional debt https://t.co/Gbf87vp2JR</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 08:15:02</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The coronavirus crisis gives swindlers a new opening. Be on the lookout for these text, email and phone scams. https://t.co/snzCArmDGe</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 08:00:19</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The IRS has extended more tax-filing and payment deadlines to July 15 after pleas from business groups and preparers, expanding on relief for individuals https://t.co/YbK9FmqFtN</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 07:30:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">From @WSJopinion: Surgeon General Jerome Adams was right: Coronavirus is our Pearl Harbor, a textbook study in catastrophic public failure, writes @DanHenninger  https://t.co/GExh5UuZmA</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 07:15:06</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">A normally busy spring real-estate market has hit the brakes, as sellers delay listing their homes because of the pandemic https://t.co/dMLt11ukCo</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 06:30:06</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">? Listen: In today's episode of The Journal podcast, @EricMorath explains how the flood of applicants for unemployment benefits in the last three weeks is overwhelming state systems and leaving many people without payments https://t.co/HtRA1nFhM1</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 06:15:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">After a disappointing Super Tuesday, Bernie Sanders homed in on Michigan. His loss there made clear that he faced a nearly insurmountable path to the nomination. https://t.co/90haj9q69H</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 06:00:16</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The coronavirus crisis has rushed the transition to telemedicine, and many health-care providers say there is no going back https://t.co/JyysB0YYbY</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 05:45:06</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">EU finance ministers agree to half a trillion euro package to cushion coronavirus crisis impact https://t.co/ZUUqEJLrZs</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 05:30:14</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">"We are at a critical junction in the life of the Postal Service," the postmaster general said. The virus will drain it of $22 billion over 18 months. https://t.co/kTy1rCcGDL</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 05:15:11</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The federal Covid-19 task force headed by Vice President Mike Pence this week discussed the prospect with meatpackers and food producers, according to people involved in the talks https://t.co/udXTnwE8e1</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 05:00:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Joe Biden made an early effort to unite Democrats behind his White House bid Thursday, announcing two new policy proposals related to health care and education https://t.co/Lj1qUGCIMO</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 04:45:06</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The closing of restaurants due to coronavirus forces tough decisions like the one at a Wisconsin farm to dump 6,000 gallons of milk into a manure pit https://t.co/2etdKyuGED</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 04:30:03</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The coronavirus pandemic has consumers choosing to order in instead of heading out for a grocery store run. But they are craving some delivery options more than others. @WSJheard explains. #WSJWhatsNow https://t.co/x7lcJUvSpI https://t.co/gD0ipDKWVY</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 04:00:00</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Record-setting jobless claims and dire economic forecasts are giving fresh urgency to the debate over how rapidly coronavirus-fueled restrictions should be pared back so the economy can begin its revival https://t.co/iVNGwZyVyS</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 03:45:08</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Do your children need a break from online school? @juliejargon has a couple of resources for digital fun. #WSJWhatsNow https://t.co/y6Aa0lejsR https://t.co/MtVVmzRCK3</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 03:30:00</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">People walk up to a shed where a priest hears their confession. A boom box playing Gregorian chants provides some privacy. https://t.co/jERwLvpk5H</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 03:15:04</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">U.K. Prime Minister Boris Johnson, who has been battling Covid-19, left intensive care as his condition has improved, his office said. He remains in the hospital for monitoring. https://t.co/ixfGxk4e36</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 02:35:37</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Chinese doctors who have for months treated coronavirus patients with chloroquine say there is no clear evidence the anti-malarial drug is effective https://t.co/oLGX1E8yAV</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 01:59:02</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">With millions of Americans suddenly out of work, Amazon warehouses have become a haven for people of all walks of life https://t.co/rt4e81ZYJI</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 01:46:20</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Saudi Arabia and Russia agreed in principle on a deal to carry out the biggest organized oil production cuts in decades, after a month-long feud that devastated oil prices https://t.co/xNyAUt8S5N</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 01:34:45</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">From @WSJopinion: The WHO is broken, compromised, and consistently acting to placate China rather than protect public health, writes @lanheechen of the @HooverInst and @Stanford https://t.co/PUOKyo8uDp</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 01:15:04</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Most U.S. states have imposed lockdown measures restricting gathering and social contact, disrupting the lives of hundreds of millions of people and the operations of thousands of businesses https://t.co/RbmMi2t80D</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 01:00:14</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">A U.S. sailor from the USS Theodore Roosevelt who had tested positive for a coronavirus infection was moved to intensive care Thursday, in the most serious case to confront sailors of the aircraft carrier https://t.co/j3d5ikeOTP</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 12:30:06</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">What does Alexis Ohanian do to relax? This AI robot guessed for him. #WSJWhatsNow https://t.co/3b7X2t4wrF</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-10 12:00:00</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Collecting enough signatures to qualify for election has gotten much tougher in the age of social distancing https://t.co/uia1URO7a7</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-09 11:45:05</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">Freelance, self-employed and gig workers are now eligible for unemployment benefits, but many say the filing process is confusing and difficult https://t.co/zCRyQDIw1C</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-09 11:30:10</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">What snags has the U.S. hit in expanding testing for the new coronavirus? What treatments are in the works? Here's what we know about the state of testing and treatment https://t.co/sqebmnl7cx</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-09 11:15:07</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">The first state in the nation with a Covid-19 case used its head start with the pandemic to avoid a potential catastrophe  https://t.co/scJLdYZx5m</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-09 11:00:10</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="user_id">WSJ</field>
    <field name="tweets_content">As China is gradually reopening for business, Western auto makers with a strong presence there are getting a boost https://t.co/2AMtNfsJ1o</field>
    <field name="created_on">2020-04-09 08:45:06</field>
  </doc>
</add>
